{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_12_9ZF2IP",
                "player_4_9ZF2IP",
                "player_5_9ZF2IP"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                12,
                4,
                5
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    10633.714,
                    -3799.959,
                    186.773,
                    0,
                    67.15233527761694,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    10526.355,
                    -3754.336,
                    185.988,
                    0,
                    -139.78876382147197,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    10413.894,
                    -4168.73,
                    180.113,
                    0.0,
                    -90.001,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            10598.389,
            -3491.627,
            188.71
        ],
        "sample_radius": 901.8138583556188
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            9993.956,
            -4183.045,
            170.939,
            0,
            27.424315793071827,
            0
        ],
        [
            10028.504,
            -3399.405,
            181.547,
            0,
            -45.69044166123383,
            0
        ],
        [
            9936.829,
            -3819.247,
            172.547,
            0,
            -8.554155263867628,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are present in this desert environment?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene possess a light skin tone?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Considering all the people in the scene, how many are confirmed to be not bald?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many individuals are both female and have a light skin color?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Among all the people in the scene, how many are neither bald nor wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "B. standing"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouching"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. picking up an object",
                    "B. putting down an object",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. looking around"
                ],
                "answer": "A. picking up an object"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. To the front of",
                    "C. To the back of",
                    "D. Below"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. Directly behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}